Guide to the Fisher and Levy Archives MSS.372
Fales Library and Special Collections
Fisher and Levy Archives
1978-2006
Fales Library and Special Collections
Fisher & Levy
Fisher, Chip (Charles)
MSS.372
0.25 Linear Feet in 1 half manuscript box.
Fisher & Levy was a New York City catering business established by Chip Fisher and Doug Levy in 1983. Fisher & Levy offered high-end, corporate catering services as well as individual takeout items. This collection contains materials created and collected by the Fisher & Levy catering company. Materials include press clippings, correspondence from customers, certificates, and menus. Materials date from 1978 to 2006.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Chip Fisher, 2013. The accession number associated with this gift is 2013.372.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
Historical Note
Fisher & Levy was a New York City catering business established by Chip Fisher and Doug Levy in 1983. Fisher & Levy offered daily corporate catering services as well as individual takeout items from their storefront location in Sutton Place. The catering company focused on providing high-end meals and food items tailored to appeal to a sophisticated, corporate clientele. Chip Fisher, a former IBM salesperson, handled the overall business, while Doug Levy, chef, was in charge of the cooking.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials created and collected by the Fisher & Levy catering company. A majority of the collection contains press clippings regarding the company, and the owners Chip Fisher and Doug Levy. A smaller portion of the collection contains correspondence from customers, certificates, and menus. Materials date from 1978 to 2006.
Caterers and Catering.; Restaurants.; Fisher, Chip (Charles); Levy, Doug
- Clippings and correspondence, 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Clippings, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Clippings and correspondence, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Clippings, 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Clippings, 1983-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Clippings and correspondence, 1984-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Menus, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Certificates, 1989-2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Clippings and correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)